Register of the Archives of the Soviet communist party and Soviet state microfilm collection: Russian State Archive of Contemporary History (Rossiiskii gosudarstvennyi arkhiv noveishei istorii - RGANI)
Hoover Institution Archives
- Fond 6, The Party Control Commission of the TsK VKP(b), 1934-1952, the Party Control Committee of the TsK KPSS, 1952-1962, the Party Commission of the TsK KPSS, 1962-1966
  - Opis 3, Minutes of the Committee for Party Control (KPK) of the TsK KPSS, 1952-1956; 120 reels (Reel 1.509-1.629)
    - XIX Convocation: Minutes of the Party Control Commission of the TsK KPSS, with Memos Issued by KPK Staff Members, 1952-1956 (Opis 3, Reel 1.509-1.629)
      - Minutes no. 118 of 24 April 1953, no 119 of 25 April 1953, no. 120 of 27 April 1953, no. 121 of 28 April 1953, and no. 122 of 29 April 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 24-29 April 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.528, File 132-136)
      - Minutes no. 123 of 30 April 1953, no 124 of 5 May 1953, and no. 125 of 6 May 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 126 of 7, 8, 11, 13, and 15 May 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 126 of 7, 8, 11, 13, and 15 May 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (facsimile copy); minutes no. 127 of 7 May 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 30 April - 15 May 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.529, File 137-142)
      - Minutes no. 128 of 9 May 1953, no 129 of 12 May 1953, no. 130 of 13 May 1953, and no. 131 of 14 May 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 132 (paragraphs 1c - 49c) of 15, 19, 20, 22, 25, and 27-29 May 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 132 of 15, 19, 20, 22, 25, and 27-29 May 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (facsimile copy), 9-29 May 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.530, File 143-149)
      - Minutes no. 133 of 16 May 1953, no 134 of 19 May 1953, no. 135 of 20 May 1953, no. 136 of 21 May 1953, and no. 137 of 23 May 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 16-23 May 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.531, File 150-154)
      - Minutes no. 138 of 25 May 1953, no 139 of 26 May 1953, no. 140 of 27 May 1953, and no. 141 of 28 May 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 25-28 May 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.532, File 155-158)
      - Minutes no. 142 of 29 May 1953, no 143 of 30 May 1953, and no. 144 of 2 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 145 of 1, 5, 10, 12, 15, and 17 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 145 of 1, 5, 10, 12, 15, and 17 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (facsimile copy); minutes no. 146 of 3 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 29 May - 17 June 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.533, File 159-164)
      - Minutes no. 147 of 4 June 1953, no 148 of 6 June 1953, no. 149 of 9 June 1953, no. 150 of 10 June 1953, no. 151 of 11 June 1953, and no. 152 of 13 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 4-13 June 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.534, File 165-170)
      - Minutes no. 153 of 16 June 1953, no 154 of 17 June 1953, no. 155 of 18 June 1953, and no. 156 of 19 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 16-19 June 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.535, File 171-174)
      - Minutes no. 157 of 20 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 158 of 19, 22-24, 26, 27, and 29 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 158 of 19, 22-24, 26, 27, and 29 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (facsimile copy); minutes no. 159 of 23 June 1953 and no. 160 of 24 June of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 19-29 June 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.536, File 175-179)
      - Minutes no. 161 of 25 June 1953, no 162 of 26 June 1953, no. 163 of 27 June 1953, and no. 164 of 29 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 25-29 June 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.537, File 180-183)
      - Minutes no. 165 of 30 June 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 166 (paragraphs 1c - 36c) of 1, 6, 8, 10, 13, 15, and 16 July 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 166 of 1, 6, 8, 10, 13, 15, and 16 July 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (facsimile copy); minutes no. 167 of 2 July 1953, no. 168 of 4 July 1953 and no. 169 of 6 July 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 30 June - 16 July 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.538, File 184-190)
      - Minutes no. 170 of 7 July 1953, no 171 of 9 July 1953, no. 172 of 11 July 1953, and no. 173 of 14 July 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 7-14 July 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.539, File 191-194)
      - Minutes no. 174 of 16 July 1953, no. 175 of 17 July 1953, no. 176 of 18 July 1953, and no. 177 of 21 July 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 178 of 17, 20-24, 27, 29, and 31 July 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 178 of 17, 20-24, 27, 29, and 31 July 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (facsimile copy), 16-31 July 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.540, File 195-200)
      - Minutes no. 179 of 23 July 1953, no 180 of 25 July 1953, no. 181 of 28 July 1953, and no. 182 of 30 July 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 17-30 July 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.541, File 201-204)
      - Minutes no. 183 of 31 July 1953 and no. 184 of 1 August 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 185 of 3-5, 7, 10, 12, and 14 August 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 185 of 3-5, 7, 10, 12, and 14 August 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (facsimile copy); minutes no. 186 of 4 August 1953 and no. 187 of 6 August 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 31 July - 3 October 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.542, File 205-210)
      - Minutes no. 188 of 7 August 1953, no. 189 of 11 August 1953, no. 190 of 13 August 1953, and no. 191 of 15 August 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 192 of 17, 19, 21, 24, 26, and 26 August 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials, 7-28 August 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.543, File 211-215)
      - Minutes no. 192 of 17, 19, 21, 24, 26, and 26 August 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 193 of 18 August 1953, no. 194 of 20 August 1953, no. 195 of 21 August 1953, and no. 196 of 22 August 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 17-28 August 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.544, File 216-220)
      - Minutes no. 197 of 25 August 1953, no. 198 of 26 August 1953, no. 199 of 27 August 1953, no. 200 of 29 August 1953, and no. 201 of 1 September 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 25 August - 1 September 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.545, File 221-225)
      - Minutes no. 202 of 2, 7, 9, 11, 14, and 15 September 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 202 of 2, 7, 9, 11, 14, and 15 September 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 203 of 3 September 1953, no. 204 of 5 September 1953, no. 205 of 8 September 1953, no. 206 of 10 September 1953, and no. 207 of 12 September 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 2-15 September 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.546, File 226-232)
      - Minutes no. 208 of 15 September 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 209 (paragraphs 1c-51c) of 16, 18, 21, 23, 25, 28, 29, and 30 September 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 209 of 16, 18, 21, 23, 25, 28, 29, and 30 September 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 210 of 17 September 1953, no. 211 of 19 September 1953, no. 212 of 22 September 1953, and no. 213 of 24 September 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 15 September - 4 December 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.547, File 233-240)
      - Minutes no. 214 of 26 September 1953, no. 215 of 29 September 1953, no. 216 of 30 September 1953, no. 217 of 1 October 1953, and no. 218 of 2 October 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 219 of 2, 5, 7, 9, 10, 12, and 14 October 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 219 of 2, 5, 7, 9, 10, 12, and 14 October 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 220 of 3 October 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 26 September - 14 December 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.548, File 241-248)
      - Minutes no. 221 of 5 October 1953, no. 222 of 6 October 1953, no. 223 of 7 October 1953, no. 224 of 8 October 1953, no. 225 of 10 October 1953, and no. 226 of 13 October 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 5-13 October 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.549, File 249-254)
      - Minutes no. 227 of 19 October 1953, no. 228 of 20 October 1953, no. 229 of 22 October 1953, no. 230 of 24 October 1953, and no. 231 of 28 October 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 232 of 16, 17, 21, 23, 24, 26-28, and 30 October 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 232 of 16, 17, 21, 23, 24, 26-28, and 30 October 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy), 16-30 October 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.550, File 255-261)
      - Minutes no. 233 of 31 October 1953, no. 234 of 3 November 1953, no. 235 of 5 November 1953, no. 236 of 6 November 1953, and no. 237 of 9 November 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 238 of 2, 4, 5, 11, and 13 November 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 238 of 2, 4, 5, 11, and 13 November 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 239 of 10 November 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 31 October - 13 November 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.551, File 262-269)
      - Minutes no. 240 of 12 November 1953, no. 241 of 14 November 1953, no. 242 of 17 November 1953, no. 243 of 19 November 1953, and no. 244 of 21 November 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 245 of 18, 20, 23, 25, and 27 November 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 245 of 18, 20, 23, 25, and 27 November 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 246 of 23 November 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 12-27 November 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.552, File 270-277)
      - Minutes no. 247 of 24 November 1953, no. 2481 of 25 November 1953, no. 249 of 26 November 1953, no. 250 of 27 November 1953, no. 251 of 28 November 1953, and no. 252 of 1 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 24 November - 1 December 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.553, File 278-283)
      - Minutes no. 253 of 3 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 254 of 2-4, 8, 9, 11, and 14 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 254 of 2-4, 8, 9, 11, and 14 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 255 of 8 December 1953, no. 256 of 11 December 1953, no. 257 of 12 December 1953, and no. 258 of 15 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 2-15 December 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.554, File 284-290)
      - Minutes no. 259 of 18 December 1953, no. 260 of 21 December 1953, and no. 261 of 22 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 262 of 16, 23-25, and 30 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes 262 of 16, 23-25, and 30 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 263 of 23 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), 16 December 1953 - 18 January 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.555, File 291-296)
      - Minutes no. 264 of 24 December 1953, no. 265 of 25 December 1953, no. 266 of 26 December 1953, no. 267 of 28 December 1953, and no. 268 of 29 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 24-29 December 1953 (Opis 3, Reel 1.556, File 297-301)
      - Minutes no. 269 of 30 December 1953; minutes no. 270 of 31 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals); memos issued by KPK staff members for minutes no. 270 of 31 December 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS; minutes no. 271 of 4 January 1953 and no. 272 of 5 January 1953 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 30 December 1953 - 5 January 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.557, File 302-306)
      - Minutes no. 273 of 6 January 1954, no. 274 of 7 January 1954, no. 275 of 11 January 1954, and no. 276 of 12 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 277 of 8 and 12-26 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes 277 of 8 and 12-26 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 278 of 14 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 6 January - 19 February 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.558, File 307-313)
      - Minutes no. 279 of 15 January 1954 and no. 280 of 16 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 281 of 18, 22, and 29 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes 281 of 18, 22, and 29 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 282 of 23 January 1954, no. 283 of 25 January 1954, and no. 284 of 26 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 15-29 January 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.559, File 314-320)
      - Minutes no. 285 of 27 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 286 of 16 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals); memos issued by KPK staff members for minutes no. 286 of 16 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS; minutes no. 287 of 29 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 288 of 30 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), 27-30 January 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.560, File 321-325)
      - Memos issued by KPK staff members for minutes no. 288 of 30 January 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS; minutes no. 289 of 1 February 1954, no. 290 of 2 February 1954, and no. 291 of 3 February 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 292 of 4-6, 8, and 12 February 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials, 30 January - 8 March 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.561, File 326-330)
      - Minutes no. 292 of 4-6, 8, and 12 February 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 293 of 6 February 1954, no. 294 of 8 February 1954, no. 295 of 9 February 1954, no. 296 of 10 February 1954, no. 297 of 11 February 1954, no. 298 of 13 February 1954, and no. 299 of 15 February 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 4-15 February 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.562, File 331-338)
      - Minutes no. 300 of 16 February 1954, no. 301 of 17 February 1954, and no. 302 of 18 February 1954; minutes no. 303 of 17, 19, and 22 February 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 303 of 17, 19, and 22 February 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 304 of 20 February 1954, no. 305 of 22 February 1954, no. 306 of 23 February 1954, no. 307 of 25 February 1954, no. 308 of 3 March 1954, and no. 309 of 4 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 16 February - 4 March 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.563, File 339-349)
      - Minutes no. 310 of 5 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 311 of 1, 2, 5, 6, 13, and 14 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 311 of 1, 2, 5, 6, 13, and 14 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 312 of 6 March 1954, no. 313 of 8 March 1954, and no. 314 of 9 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 1 March - 6 April 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.564, File 350-355)
      - Minutes no. 315 of 9 March 1954, no. 316 of 10 March 1954, no. 317 of 11 March 1954, no. 318 of 12 March 1954, no. 319 of 13 March 1954, and no. 320 of 13 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 9-13 March 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.565, File 356-361)
      - Minutes no. 321 of 15 March 1954, no. 322 of 16 March 1954, no. 323 of 17 March 1954, no. 324 of 18 March 1954, no. 325 of 20 March 1954, no. 326 of 23 March 1954, and no. 327 of 25 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 328 of 19, 22, 25, 26, and 31 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 328 of 19, 22, 25, 26, and 31 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 329 of 27 March 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 15-31 March 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.566, File 362-371)
      - Minutes no. 330 of 29 March 1954, no. 331 of 30 March 1954, no. 332 of 31 March 1954, and no. 333 of 1 April 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 334 (paragraphs 1c-21c) of 2, 3, 6, and 9 April 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials, 29 March - 9 April 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.567, File 372-376)
      - Minutes no. 334 (paragraphs 22c-46c and 1gc - 21gc) of 10, 12, and 14 April 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 334 of 2, 3, 6, 9, 10, 12, and 14 April 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 335 of 3 April 1954, no. 336 of 5 April 1954, no. 337 of 6 April 1954, no. 338 of 7 April, no. 339 of 8 April 1954, and no. 340 of 10 April of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 2-29 April 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.568, File 377-384)
      - Minutes no. 341 of 13 April 1954 and no. 342 of 15 April 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 343 of 16, 19, 23, 26, and 30 April 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 343 of 16, 19, 23, 26, and 30 April 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 344 of 16 April 1954, no. 345 and no. 346 of 17 April 1954, and no. 347 of 19 April of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 13 April - 11 May 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.569, File 385-392)
      - Minutes no. 348 of 19 April 1954, no. 349 and no. 350 of 20 April 1954, no. 351 of 22 April 1954, and no. 352 of 23 April 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 19-23 April 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.570, File 393-397)
      - Minutes no. 353 of 24 April 1954, no. 354 of 27 April 1954, no. 355 of 28 April 1954, no. 356 of 29 April 1954, no. 357 and no. 358 of 30 April 1954, and no. 359 of 4 May 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 24 April - 4 May 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.571, File 398-404)
      - Minutes no. 360 of 4, 5, 7, 8, 12, 14, and 15 May 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 360 of 4, 5, 7, 8, 12, 14, and 15 May 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 361 of 6 May 1954, no. 362 of 8 May 1954, no. 363 of 11 May 1954, no. 364 of 12 May 1954, no. 365 of 13 May 1954, and no. 366 of 15 May 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 4-29 May 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.572, File 405-412)
      - Minutes no. 367 of 18 May 1954 and no. 368 of 19 May 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 369 of 19, 21, 25, 26, and 28 May 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 369 of 19, 21, 25, 26, and 28 May 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 370 of 20 May 1954, no. 371 of 21 May 1954, no. 372 of 22 May 1954, and no. 373 of 22 May 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 15 May - 7 June 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.573, File 413-420)
      - Minutes no. 374 of 24 May 1954, no. 375 of 25 May 1954, no. 376 of 26 May 1954, no. 377 of 27 May 1954, and no. 378 of 29 May 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 24-29 May 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.574, File 421-425)
      - Minutes no. 379 and no. 380 of 31 May 1954, no. 381 of 1 June 1954, no. 382 of 2 June 1954, and no. 383 of 3 June 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 384 of 4, 5, 8, 10-12, 15, and 17 June 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials, 31 May - 28 June 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.575, File 426-431)
      - Minutes no. 384 of 4, 5, 8, 10-12, 15, and 17 June 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 385 of 4 June 1954, no. 386 of 5 June 1954, no. 387 of 8 June 1954, no. 388 of 9 June 1954, no. 389 of 10 June 1954, no. 390 of 12 June 1954, and no. 391 of 15 June 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 4-15 June 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.576, File 432-439)
      - Minutes no. 392 of 16 June 1954 and no. 393 of 17 June 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members; minutes no. 394 of 18, 19, 22, 24, 25, 28, and 29 June 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with related materials; minutes no. 394 of 18, 19, 22, 24, 25, 28, and 2 June 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (certified typed copy); minutes no. 395 of 19 June 1954, no. 396 of 22 June 1954, no. 397 of 23 June 1954, no. 398 of 24 June 1954, no. 399 of 25 June 1954, no. 400 of 26 June 1954, and no. 401 of 28 June 1954 of the KPK of the TsK KPSS (originals), with memos issued by KPK staff members, 16-29 June 1954 (Opis 3, Reel 1.577, File 440-450)